{
	"lv_1":[
		{
			"Question":"Most of the commercial buildings in Hong Kong use District Cooling System.",
			"Choice":["A. True","B. False"],
			"Ans":"B",
			"Elaborations":"Up to 2022, there are only a few districts has District Cooling System services such as Kwuv Tung North New Development Area, Kai Tak Development, Tung Chung etc. Some of these are under construction."
		},
		{
			"Question":"Is the price of District Cooling System expensive?",
			"Choice":["A. True","B. False"],
			"Ans":"B",
			"Elaborations":"In 2013/2014, the price of District Cooling System is similar to the conventional central air-conditioning systems separately installed in individual buildings. With the development of District Cooling System, the price tends to fall."
		}
		
	],
	"lv_2":[
		{
			"Question":"What is Urban Heat Island Effect?",
			"Choice":["A. Cities experience much warmer temperatures than nearby rural areas.","B. Rural areas are warmer than nearby cities to affect these cities’ temperature.","C. Both cities and rural areas are very hot.","D. There is lots of pollution in the city."],
			"Ans":"A",
			"Elaborations":"An urban heat island occurs when a city experiences much warmer temperatures than nearby rural areas. The difference in temperature between urban and less-developed rural areas has to do with how well the surfaces in each environment absorb and hold heat."
		},
		{
			"Question":"How can the District Cooling System reduce the Urban Heat Island Effect?",
			"Choice":["A. It cools down the cities to reduce the temperature.","B. It saves the cost and the firms can have more capital for environment.","C. It saves the area to plant trees, other vegetation etc.","D. The factory of the District Cooling System can reduce the Urban Heat Island Effect."],
			"Ans":"C",
			"Elaborations":"Method of reducing Urban Heat Island Effect: \n\t 1. Build green infrastructure improvements into regular street upgrades and capital improvement projects to ensure continued investment in heat-reducing practices.\n\t2.	Plant trees and other vegetation. \n\t3. Build green roofs—Green roofs are an ideal heat island reduction strategy, providing both direct and ambient cooling effects.  In addition, green roofs improve air quality by reducing the heat island effect and absorbing pollutants.\nFor the District Cooling System : No vibration / noise, reduce heat island effect, more flexible building design e.g. green roof, since no chiller plant is required."
		},
		{
			"Question":"When did Hong Kong government start the research of district cooling?",
			"Choice":["A. 1980","B.	1990","C. 1997","D. 2022"],
			"Ans":"C",
			"Elaborations":" "
		}
	],
	"lv_3":[
		{
			"Question":"Kai Tak DCS in 2013 to 2019-20 as an example, how many carbon emissions does the District Cooling System reduce?",
			"Choice":["A. 14 210 tonnee","B. 15 210 tonnes" ,"C.	20 210 tonnes","D. 11 210 tonnes"],
			"Ans":"A",
			"Elaborations":"The total estimated electricity saving from the commencement of operation of the Kai Tak DCS in 2013 to 2019-20 is about 20.3 million kWh (the total estimated electricity cost saving is about $ 24 million), which is equivalent to a reduction in carbon emissions of 14 210 tonnes."
		},
		{
			"Question":"Which of the following is the main component in the District Cooling System?",
			"Choice":["A. Fan motor","B. Condenser fan","C.	Blower motor","D.	Louver","E. Central Chiller Plant"],
			"Ans":"E",
			"Elaborations":"A typical DCS comprises the following components:\n\t- Central Chiller Plant - generate chilled water for cooling purposes.\n\t- Distribution Network - distribute chilled water to buildings. \n\t - Consumer Substation - interface with buildings' own air-conditioning circuits."
		},
		{
			"Question":"Which of the following sentence(s) about the benefits of District Cooling System is correct?",
			"Choice":["A. Energy Saving","B. Reduce Refrigerant Usage","C. Reduce Noise Pollution","D. Improve City Skyline","E. All are correct"],
			"Ans":"E",
			"Elaborations":" "
		},
		{
			"Question":"Arrange the following steps of District Cooling System in ascending order.\n(i)	User buildings\n(ii)	Underground water pipe network\n(iii)	Central Chiller Plant\n(iv)	Heat Exchangers",
			"Choice":["A. i, iv, ii, iii","B. iii, ii, iv, i ","C. iv ,ii, iii, i","D. iii, iv, ii, i","E.	i, ii, iv, iii"],
			"Ans":"B",
			"Elaborations":"District cooling system (DCS) distributes chilled water through network of underground pipes from central chiller plant to multiple buildings for air-conditioning."
		},
		{
			"Question":"Kai Tak DCS in 2013 to 2019-20 as an example, which is/ are the key component(s) of the charge?",
			"Choice":["A. Capacity Charge","B. Consumption Charge","C. Electricity Charge","D. All of the above","E. Both A and B"],
			"Ans":"E",
			"Elaborations":"The key components of the charge are:\n\t1. Capacity Charge\n\t\tCalculated based on the contract capacity and the capacity charge rate applicable to the building;\n\t2. Consumption Charge\n\t\tCalculated based on the actual cooling energy consumption of the building in the month and the consumption charge rate applicable to the building."
		},
		{
			"Question":"What is the Capacity Charge Rate in 2022/23?",
			"Choice":["A. $ 133.26 per kilowatt refrigeration per month","B. $ 143.26 per kilowatt refrigeration per month","C.	$ 153.36 per kilowatt rfrigeration per month","D. $ 163.5 per kilowatt refrigeration per month"],
			"Ans":"A",
			"Elaborations":""
		},
		{
			"Question":"What is the Consumption Charge Rate in 2022/23?",
			"Choice":["A. $0.2068 per kilowatt-hour refrigeration","B. $0.2188 per kilowatt-hour refrigeration","C. $0.2268 per kilowatt-hour refrigeration","D. $0.2288 per kilowatt-hour refrigeration"],
			"Ans":"B",
			"Elaborations":""
		}
	]
}
